Berke Kiran

Game Developer

berkekiranofficial@hotmail.com <u>berkekiran.com</u> <u>linkedin.com/in/berkekiran</u>

ABOUT

Hi! I'm Berke Kiran a self-taught Game Developer for 12+ years. I like to write game & film stories for 16+ years.

All these years, I'm focusing to improve my skills to be a game studio lead.

These skills are: programming, 3d modelling (hard surface & organic models), texturing, rigging and animating, VFX design, UI/UX design, sound design, level design, game design, writing scripts/stories, marketing, game project management and financial management of game studio.

If you have a project you'd like to discuss, feel free to reach out.

EXPERIENCE

Backpack Games, Turkey— Unity Developer

JUNE 2020 - AUGUST 2020 (Internship)

Linetec Studio, Germany — Character Artist

JULY 2018 - DECEMBER 2018 (Freelance)

TaleWorlds Entertainment, Turkey— 3D Artist

JUNE 2018 - JULY 2018 (Internship)

Ekim Gida, Turkey — IT Specialist

JULY 2013 - AUGUST 2013 (Internship)

Uludag Ihracatcilar Birligi, Turkey — IT Specialist

JULY 2012 - AUGUST 2012 (Internship)

EDUCATION

Karabuk University, Turkey — Bachelor of Computer Engineering - GPA: 3.0/4.0

SEPTEMBER 2015 – SEPTEMBER 2021

OIB Automotive Technical High School, Turkey — IT Database Programming - Diploma Score: 87/100

SEPTEMBER 2011 – JUNE 2015

Graduated in 2015 with a class rank of second out of 724 graduates.

AWARDS Next In Game - Next Game Startup 2021 Third Award, OIB - Outstanding Achievement Certificate